It's starting Master, it's starting Master, it's starting Master, it's starting Master, it's starting Master, it's starting Master, it's starting Master, it's starting Master.
It's starting, Master.
Nyonya's picking flowers... and she can't stop smelling them.
Newly, I smell it.
He's smelling it, Master.
Tell 200 people that they smell it.
Is smell a medical term?
I don't like that.
It's starting...
It's started... It's started...
Anyway, I learned a lot this week.
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
I've lived for over 50 years and I still didn't know about this...
I mean, I've been to Yokohama, Chinatown, etc., and I've probably eaten there, yes, I've eaten there.
I've grown up without anyone pointing it out to me.
Well, I'm sure you can tell us about it on air.
I'm looking forward to your continued support today.
I've cut my hair or something...
I don't know...
It's fashionable. It's all the rage in town.
There were girls with short bangs and asymmetrical hair.
What's the matter? I got a bug.
My hair was getting long, and the bangs were a little long. My mom noticed. She said she'd cut them off.
She used to be a hairdresser.
So I thought I'd ask her. I thought it was a favor.
I thought it was a favor, and it's true, it's a lot of work to go to the salon and all that, just for bangs.
So I asked her to cut them and left it completely to her, and when she was done, she told me that maybe I cut them a little too long.
And I was like, "Well, well, well.
I came to tvk without looking in the mirror, thinking that since I was a former hairdresser, I'd be fine.
But it's not funny at all.
I'm glad I had my hat
I'm glad I had the hat
Short, isn't it? Short?
It's a little short for a guy in his 20s
I wonder if he was 5, he'd look cute and childish
Yes, it would look childish.
What are you going to do with it?
I'm going to eat a lot of wakame seaweed.
Yes, I'm going to stretch it. Can't I just stretch it here?
Is it wrong here? I don't think so.
No?
I'll do the wakame and the money, but if I have a make-up artist make it look a little better... it'll look totally different from the book.
I don't think it's fen in the book... you're so worried about it, I'm worried about it too...
I'll ask him to take off his hat.
It's not bad at all.
Oh, really? Oh, so it's okay?
It's more refreshing, isn't it?
Mom, it was fine. It wasn't short.
There's nothing wrong with your mother.
Yes, it is.
I miss the mother cut.
Did you have it cut?
Of course. I had a mother's haircut all through elementary school.
But once I entered junior high school, things changed a bit.
You know how I dressed up?
I don't know if it was my first time at the hairdresser or the beauty parlor. I think my local classmate's father runs it.
It was the first time I had been to the salon, but before that, my mother, my mother is not a hairdresser or anything like that anymore.
I remember that she had a pretty bold haircut or something.
Really?
She cuts it like this now.
Wow! It's a haircut!
I'm going to cut it like this.
Wow! Wow!
Put a newspaper underneath, like this.
Yes! There you have it! Like that.
That's so bold!
Well, it was like that in the Showa period.
Generally.
That's right.
Especially for boys, it was so embarrassing. They go to beauty salons and such.
Really?
On the contrary?
Yes, that's right. That's why I probably don't go to a hair salon,
It wasn't until late in junior high school that I heard that a girl's haircut at a salon makes her look fashionable,
I heard about fashionable haircuts, and I said, "Where is it? I said, "Where, where, where?
So I went to a place a little bit far away for the first time and had my hair cut. At that time, I think...
Myoujo, there is a celebrity magazine called Heibon, isn't there? He had a clipping of a match from Myojo or something.
I wonder what the matches were like back then.
I don't know, it wasn't a borrowed match, but a regular match.
I don't remember if it was Match or someone else, but anyway, please make your hair like that.
It's embarrassing to think about it now. I was a complete novice at the time, so I asked him to do my hair like that.
I was just on top of him, so after the match, he said, "Your hair is different from Match's.
He didn't say, "That's not your face.
I was bold to hold the folded match without any embarrassment.
I did that, yes. But don't you still do it now? People do it.
Like, "Please give me the same haircut as this person." I do it a lot.
What? Did something happen? With someone.
I want you to do my hair the same as Sisungjoon's.
He's an actor.
Only the fringe is short.
This is just for now. My mother's style.
Sisung, are you saying only the bangs are short? No, but it was see-through, like see-through bangs.
Boys like it when the source is good, no matter what kind of haircut they have, but... most of the time.
Subtle boys? That's what they're so good at.
I'm a bit peculiar. I've said it before. I have a lot of knots.
There you go. - Is that right?
There are two on the top and two on this side.
What? What do you mean? Like there's a lot of thumbs?
Yes, some people have a lot of them.
Isn't there just one for each of you?
No, not one.
And they're not spirals.
That's why it's so peculiar and you can't cut it normally.
Then, while covering it up...
So the collar was relatively long.
So, if you cut it short and put it up tentatively, you'll get the vortex here.
What do you do before? Do you have a regular hairdresser? I have a favorite place. I usually get it cut at the same place.
But it's been this long now, and when it's this long, the girls don't have much of an influence on me.
I don't have much influence on the girls. I have a request for this haircut. I'm going to do a ponytail, so please leave this part alone. I'm going to do a ponytail, so please leave this part here and cut this part here.
I ask for this part to be this long, and then I cut a few millimeters more here and a little less there, but the back is just fine.
But the back is just fine. It's a girl's club. The men's club is the same, but maybe this time of year...
For example...
For example, when students go from junior high school to high school, or from elementary school to junior high school, they tend to change their hair. You know, a makeover.
You know, like, "I'm going to change my look. I'm sure that's possible. I would love for you to have a photo of her with her match.
But maybe he's fashionable in a roundabout way. Yes, he is. That's why he seems so young.
And the person who cuts the hair, too. I see. You can't really explain it in words, can you? No, it's all in my imagination.
So, I would like to encourage everyone to give it a try.
I really want you to try it.
It's just the time of year for me, isn't it?
I'm going to change my hairstyle.
I'll be starting a new life soon.
And that's why
Today's topic is...
Let's see...
It's already March.
It's March.
Well, a little bit, isn't it?
March
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
5 days, 15 days, 15 days, today is actually, oh, that means yesterday was White Day, right, right, what's up, guys?
What's the matter, ladies and gentlemen, did you get the ski equipment that I bought you, the ski equipment that I gave you back, not the ski equipment?
I keep getting it wrong... it's Shoe Day... the anniversary of shoes...
Shoes are Western footwear.
Until the Edo period, everyone used to wear zori (slippers) or geta (slippers).
But in the Meiji Era, the so-called "modern shoes" were introduced.
This type of shoes came from the West.
That was in 1870, the 3rd year of Meiji.
On that day, the first shoe factory was built in Japan.
Wow, that's amazing!
At first, the shape of our feet were totally different from Westerners', right?
Not really. Because we are from the East, our feet are basically flat.
Western people have feet like this.
I was a little concerned about the intonation of the Nike Air Max.
I thought they looked a little uncomfortable when I first put them on.
I thought they were too thin.
I'm not sure if you don't mind, but I'm pretty flat, so this is how I feel.
So, normal, foreign-made shoes don't fit me at all.
I see. I'm sure you'll be fine. I'm fine too. I'm very flat.
So narrow!
They're narrow... basically foreign ones are narrow.
I think I'm wide even if I say they're narrow.
For example, Adidas also has a wide version.
I didn't know that. Adidas? Adidas Adidas Adidas Adidas Adidas Adidas
You mean Nike Adidas?
Adidas!
Is there a wide Adidas?
They're called "wide".
Is that so?
By the way, Japanese makers
ASICS, for example, has "wide" and "extra wide".
Or, to be more precise, they have "extra wide".
Extra wide!
Even I can't find extra wide ones.
Even I'm wide!
That's why I'm so frustrated.
It's like there's someone who's a lot thicker than me.
I see.
Recently, you know...
You said you've been walking around a lot. I've been walking around a lot and smiling.
That's why I'm so concerned about my shoes.
For short distances, even if they don't fit, but for longer distances...
But over a long distance, the narrow width of the shoes makes me feel like I'm being squeezed.
I know a lot of things now.
I've been to the shoe store and tried them on and said, "Wow, they're really tight!
I'm not like that. So, especially for someone like me with my feet, if you had flat feet like that, I think you'd be really interested in them.
I'm sure you'd be really interested in them, especially if you have flat feet like mine.
My partner is trying on all kinds of shoes, and Singo is doing exactly the same thing.
He's totally different. Like, "I can't get into these shoes, I can't get into my Converse, etc.
So I think it's the same for Shingo.
Nike shoes are basically narrow.
But of course they're not so narrow that you can't wear them.
And the design is so cool!
They're cool!
These are cool!
It says "Air" or "Air" or "Air" or "Air" or "Air" or "Air" or "Air" or "Air".
You buy them, but let's say your foot size is 27cm.
If you wear Nike shoes like that, they won't fit.
The size fits, but the width doesn't. But if you put on a pair 0.5 or 1 centimeter larger, you can get some room.
I think Shingo is probably doing something like that.
It's true that his foot size is almost the same as mine, but he says, "He's too big.
It's true that my foot size is almost the same as yours, but it takes a lot of effort to get a bigger foot.
So you're okay with that, too.
I'm surprised at how different shoes are now that I'm older, even for sneakers.
I'm very surprised every day. It's very important, isn't it?
Feet, you know. Feet.
It's true that they are hard to meet, aren't they, in the old days?
Especially now, the shape of Japanese people's body is still the same.
The shape of the feet is also very different from the old days.
I mean...
You've been influenced by the West.
I've been wearing shoes since I was little.
Of course...
That's the way to go.
I heard it was difficult in the beginning.
First of all, the shoes coming from the West were huge.
Japanese people's body shape changed a lot.
We didn't know what size shoes they were back then, so even if we were told what size shoes they were, they were too big and too bulky.
I guess they had big feet.
In the old days, it was normal for 160cm boys to be over 160cm or 160cm, wasn't it? That's right.
Over 170 cm now? No, I'm about that height now.
They've grown a lot, haven't they?
I also thought that even from our time, say from the Showa period, the shape of the face was already a little different from what it is today.
I think they're tiny now. I think they're all tiny now because they don't eat hard food?
Because they don't eat hard food, they're more developed here first of all.
So, you know, there's always, like, one or two people in the class who are like home base, and they're always nicknamed home base.
They were always nicknamed "home base." Poor kids.
And then there's the samurai, the wild samurai, the fallen warrior, the wild, wild, wow.
In Japanese period dramas, the main characters are always in wigs like that, and the style is not to have a big face.
It's not cool if you have a small face.
He said that actors in the old days had big faces.
I don't get it.
On TV or on stage, if you're small, it's not cool.
It's better to have a little bit of belly for kimono.
It's cooler.
That's how it is.
Various things are changing, aren't they?
But if things continue as they are, everyone will get smaller and smaller, won't they?
Face?
Even now, there are a lot of tiny people.
Yes, there are.
They are getting smaller and smaller.
Don't they? Eventually, about this size.
It was a long time ago, but I saw Kyoko Koizumi for the first time in person.
Kyon-Kyon is about the same age as me, so her face was extremely tiny for that time period.
It's really only this small.
Is it true?
Really? It's like...
I was a little surprised. I think Kyonkyon was one of the smallest girls in that era.
I thought, "Wow, she's a celebrity!
All my friends were like a home base. You don't need that many home bases.
Just one... just one... just one... if you're going to make it a baseball.
I'm fine... but let's hear a letter or something...
Let's go.
Let's see...
Here we go.
Oh, wait a minute.
The latest one's here, too.
Ooh.
In real time.
There's a lot coming in.
Wait a minute, please. Amazing.
Yes, yes, yes. Oh, thank you, Minami Sakamihara for the very Devil's Touch.
Good evening, everyone. This is Devil.
Finally, Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku's 8th album, Indugo Hour, has been released!
Master! It happened during this live broadcast, didn't it?
I was hit hard from the very first song!
Please listen to Master Sarpon as well!
My own copy of the CD will be distributed to the corps members now!
Thank you so much!
I bought soooo many, probably.
Here you go.
Oh, my gosh!
They're buying a lot.
Thank you so much.
That's amazing.
And it's a Maiamma.
Yes, it is.
Uniforms, uniform team of goods
Thank you very much.
The first song is a self-introduction rap song called "Knock You Out.
Self-introduction rap song!
That song was really cool!
Thank you very much.
You're a good writer.
It was written by Kenny Daz of Umeda Cypher.
He was originally from the Ebitu family.
Really?
That's right.
There's a show called Freestyle Dungeon.
who also appeared in such a rap battle show wearing the goods.
He made it for us.
By the way, who does he like?
He liked Shoyo.
I see.
Wow, that's great!
Well, I really appreciate it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Well, well, well.
I've had a few of those.
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't know what else to say.
There's a lot of stuff.
What should we do?
Let's see...
Uh, a little bit.
There's that blue Mars again.
He's drawing again.
Wait a minute.
I'll download the picture again.
Oh! I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go!
Oh, yeah.
Really good!
There you go.
There we go.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm gonna get a head start.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Master.
You're terrible at this, Master.
What's a snot?
Right.
Why snot? Just you.
When he's doing something, he whispers "snot" really loudly.
Haribotter.
As in "Haribotter".
I said "snot" once.
That time.
Like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow.
A lot of people are checking their luggage.
Like chargers.
They tend to last a year.
There's a lot of people in our group.
They're originally from Bi-Cata.
It started with the phone.
I've never seen a dumpling bun like this.
I've never seen these dumpling buns before.
I wonder what it is
It's a lyric.
It's in the lyrics.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I see.
What a lyric!
But you're good!
You've captured the characteristics of each of them.
Yes, of course.
No, no, no, no...
Rock Valley's face is so cute.
You're right, you're right.
I have an image of her.
I have an image.
I've never seen it before in an illustration.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you very much.
So, here's the thing.
I have an announcement.
Another random bromide!
Wow!
Here it is!
Here it is again!
Tomorrow, from the 29th of February.
From tomorrow.
When it goes on sale.
For a month.
Cool master stuff.
By the way, who's this pretty girl?
Wow, she's cute.
She's so cute.
Is it all right that she's so cute?
If she's this cute, I wonder if she'll be okay in town.
The town is in an uproar.
The town will be in an uproar.
Yes or no... well, of course.
I'd like to have one.
I've got your stuff.
Like this.
So many!
It's a lot of work.
When you have more members, you have more things to do.
That's right.
Oh, that's mine.
Here it is!
It's blue!
So cool!
And the men's colors, too.
Mencaras over.
And the problem
Master is so cool, isn't it?
I see.
The guitar is upside down.
Basically, it's like...
I just want to joke around.
When you take a picture like this...
It's fine.
It's the same for everyone from the Showa era.
Most of the X pictures have funny faces.
When a camera is pointed at me and I make a normal face.
I feel like my soul will be taken away.
I want to be taken away.
When was that?
It's like that.
It's like when cameras were first made.
It's cute.
Different versions.
Yeah, there's a lot of different versions.
It's random.
So cute!
That's great.
But you know what?
I think she's the cutest.
She's adorable.
He's cute.
It's overwhelming.
Yes, it's overwhelming.
Are you okay?
It's great!
The town's going crazy.
We're already in the way.
Yes, they are.
Oh, my God.
So cute!
I might have to let go of the restrictions.
I'm not letting go of control.
That's enough!
There are more versions like this.
A lot of them.
Oh, my God!
I love this illustration.
Like this one.
So cute!
It's really nice.
It's okay.
That's why I'm asking you.
Starting tomorrow.
From tomorrow... From tomorrow...
Until March 31st
Seven-Eleven, Lawson, Family Mart, and Poplar.
We'll be selling it again.
Please get them all!
If you complete it, right?
If you complete all of them every time...
We give them away.
It's a quart card specially made for this program.
Quark card.
What?
A quota card.
What's a quark card?
What's a quo card?
You know...
At convenience stores
Stick it on...
Put it in
It's the kind of thing you put in a quotation card.
Just stick it in.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
It's like a chance to win!
Yes, yes, yes...
There are 12 cards in each of the three patterns.
What?
If you get 12 of each pattern...
I'll be okay with quaaludes.
I see.
That's right, you're going to collect them all.
That's for sure, isn't it?
I see.
Wow, but...
How many do you get for completing all of them?
Let's see...
3 patterns.
3 patterns for 12 people.
When you have completed 36 cards...
It's real real already
Real Complete.
Complete, complete, complete.
But it's random.
You know...
It's hard to get all 12.
Wow.
That's why...
You know, if you like evites...
Or if you like Sarpon.
And if you just want to get that one from Sarpon...
Random...
I'm the only one who shows up.
I want you to harass me like that.
You gotta be kidding me.
Don't fuck with me.
I'm a master.
I want all the masters.
Wow.
Here we go again... like this is crazy.
Like, "This is crazy.
Like, I'm the only one who gets it on certain days of the month.
I'm the only one who gets it on those days.
I'm a master.
I'm looking forward to working with you all.
I didn't say yes.
Well, we're almost done with the live broadcast.
How are you doing, my man?
We had a lot of recording today.
How are you doing?
How are you?
Well, yes...
Well, for now...
Is this your impression of today?
Or are these your impressions of today's recording?
Including the recording.
The guest...
It's been a while since we've had that person here.
Um...
Friends?
It's been a while since I've had a guest.
It's been a while since I've been with Friends.
I thought it was a very enjoyable time.
You know...
I've been speaking a little slowly lately during rehearsals for the play, so...
I've been speaking slowly lately in rehearsals for the play, so to get my words across... Theater Shreep 2024.
It's at the Sunshine Theatre in your backyard in March. We're doing a play in my garden.
I was in the middle of rehearsals for that.
It's been a few days, but it's been a long time since I've had someone speak this fast.
Anyway, you know, I've learned a lot of things from you before.
Anyway, we learned a lot of things this week, didn't we? I hope you will make the most of it.
I hope you all will take a look at them in the future.
I'll be back next week at 8:00 p.m., right?
I would like to ask you all to send us a letter or something like that.
I'm sure you'll be seeing a lot of new things this time of year, right?
Yes, a new life...
I'd be happy to receive your letters.
I said please, but I didn't. See you next week for the live broadcast.